{
    "subject": "Noah_Bennett",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Paloma_Lopez-Fitzgerald",
    "human_readable": "Noah Bennett is married to Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9707754850387573,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Noah Bennett and Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9429827928543091,
            "question": "Name the person who is married to Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9155554175376892,
            "question": "Who is married to Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9128813147544861,
            "question": "To whom is Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9081929922103882,
            "question": "Who is Noah Bennett married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8596314787864685,
            "question": "Does Noah Bennett have a wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8247205018997192,
            "question": "Who is Noah Bennett's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7405441999435425,
            "question": "What is the name of Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7355020046234131,
            "question": "What is the name of Noah Bennett's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.716727077960968,
            "question": "Is Noah Bennett in a relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Noah Bennett is married to Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald.",
            "html": "yago_8240_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Noah Bennett's wife?",
            "html": "yago_8240_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_8240_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Noah Bennett's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_8240_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8240_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\nThe provided text states: \"Noah and Paloma nearly wed in August 2007, but it was interrupted. The two are planning to wed sometime in the future, and enjoyed a romantic dream waltz courtesy of young Endora Lenox.\"  Later, it says \"Since 2008, Noah Bennett and Paloma have grown further away from each other as Paloma'sex-boyfriend Roberto has moved next door to them. Noah has also been forced to kiss Fancy Crane while she was being mind controlled. He was caught by Paloma and Paloma's brother Luis Lopez-Fitzgerald. This has caused tremendous stress between the two of them.\" \n\n\nThis strongly implies that they are married, or at least planning to be.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Noah Bennett and Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald are planning to wed and have nearly wed in the past. Additionally, Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald is described as Noah's wife, supporting the statement that Noah Bennett is married to Paloma Lopez-Fitzgerald."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}